他们说有力量在波士顿。
Max: They say there's power in Boston.
一些电话服务在丹佛。
Some phone service in Denver.
但事情远从是什么。
But things are far from what they were.
也许这一切都是不可避免的。
Maybe it was all inevitable.
之间不可避免的碰撞人类和技术。
An unavoidable collision between mankind and technology.
互联网是为了使世界变得更小。
The Internet was meant to make the world a smaller place.
但它实际上更小的感觉没有它。
But it actually feels smaller without it.
我知道的意志和伊夫林脚轮比任何人都好。
I knew will and Evelyn caster better than anyone.
我知道他们的辉煌。
I knew their brilliance.
他们的奉献精神到了他们认为英寸
Their dedication to what they believed in.
以及他们所喜爱。
And to what they loved.
[<I>约玛·kaukonen的“创世纪”</ I><I>播放</ I>]
[<i> Jorma kaukonen's "genesis"</i> <i> plays</i> ]
?<I>的时机已经到来</ I>的<i>我们暂停</ I>?
?<i> The time has come</i> <i> for us to pause</i> ?
?<I>和思考生活</ I><I>因为它是</ I>?
?<i> and think of living</i> <i> as it was</i> ?
[点击设备，将呼噜声]
[ device clicks, will grunts ]
?<I>进去以后</ I><I>我们必须跨越</ I>?
?<i> Into the future</i> <i> we must cross</i> ?
?<I>必须跨越</ I>?
?<i> must cross</i> ?
?<I>我想和你一起去</ I>?
?<i> I'd like to go with you</i> ?
我不知道什么样的点。
I'm not sure what the point is.
铜屏蔽电磁辐射。
Copper shields the electromagnetic radiation.
是的，我知道它是如何工作的。
Yeah, I know how it works.
我问...
I'm asking...
“为什么？”
"Why?"
保护区。
Sanctuary.
没有获得通过。任何类型的信号。
Nothing gets through. No signals of any kind.
你看？死区。什么都没有。
You see? Dead zone. Nothing.
嗯，肯定的，但你可以只是把它关掉。
Uh-huh, sure, but you could just turn it off.
是的，但少分心是你想要的，对不对？
Yeah, but fewer distractions is what you wanted, right?
是不是？[笑]
Isn't it? [ Laughs ]
是啊。这就是我想要的。
Yeah. That's what I wanted.
来吧，我们要迟到了。
Come on, we'll be late.
为了什么？
For what?
嘿，你知道吗？
Hey, you know what?
什么？
What?
我真的觉得我开始使这一进展。
I really think I'm starting to make progress on this.
嘿！
Hey
您需要穿好衣服。
You need to get dressed.
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
我不知道为什么你费心这些证据。
I don't know why you bother with these proofs.
是啊，只有三个人在世界上都不在乎。
Yeah, only three people in the world even care.
因为它的乐趣。
Because it's fun.
你确定你了为了这？
You sure you're up for this?
不，不是远程。真的吗？
No. Not remotely. Really?
请问，这是非常重要的。
Will, it's important.
我知道，但你的捐赠者是傻瓜。
I know, but your donors are fools.
他们只是坐在那里发呆
They just sit there in a daze
等着我说的话“商业应用。”
waiting for me to say the words "commercial application."
它杀死我。
It kills me.
好了，在“阿斗”今天有
Well, the "fools" there today
可以资助我们在未来5年。
could fund us for the next 5 years.
好吧，那么我想在这种情况下
Well, then I suppose in that case
是。
Yes.
但是，如果这个顺利的话，
But if this goes well,
拜托，你必须答应我，我会，
please, you have to promise me that I'll,
我永远不会有这样做再次。
I'll never have to do this ever again.
从来没有。答应。
Never. Promise.
好。我保证。
Okay. I promise.
真的吗？当然可以。
Really? Sure.
我保证。
I promise.
[笑]
[ Laughs ]
你在说谎。
You're lying.
[电台喋喋不休]
[ Radio chatter ]
[贝尔顺口溜]
[ Bell jingles ]
[不明显的谈话]
[ Indistinct conversation ]
所有：生日快乐，亲爱的亚伦！
All: Happy Birthday, dear Aaron
祝你生日快乐！
Happy Birthday to you
[鼓掌]
[ Applause ]
男人：贾森，舞台的另一侧。
Man: Jason, other side of the stage.
是的，我想要做的相机检查
Yeah, I'd like to do a camera check
和完善的检查起来。
and a sound check together.
你会做的第一个块，
You'll do the first block,
其次是麦克雷，卢埃林，以及 -
followed by mcrae, llewellyn, and --
啊，那么重头戏。
ah, then the main event.
伊夫林：最大。电动车，你怎么样？
Evelyn: Max. Ev, how are you?
好。
Good.
准备唱你吃晚饭？
Ready to sing for your supper?
我很抱歉把你通过它。
I'm sorry to put you through it.
医生施法者？抱歉。你会介意的？
Doctor caster? Sorry. Would you mind?
当然可以。
Sure thing.
谢谢。
Thanks.
什么？
What?
你有追星族？为什么我没有拿到追星族？
You have groupies? Why don't I get groupies?
对不起/打扰一下。医生水域，将你想通过做一个跑？
Excuse me. Doctor waters, would you like to do a run through?
是的，请。我会在后台看到你。好吧。
Yes, please. I'll see you backstage. Alright.
[门解锁]
[ Door unlocks ]
医生凯西：<I>重要的区别，嗯... </ I>
Doctor Casey: <i> Important distinction, um...</i>
<I>这造成脑</ I><I>是自持。</ I>
<i> This created brain</i> <i> is self-sustaining.</i>
Ⅰ和它的能力，呃，</ I>的情绪表达的<I>。</ I>
<i> And it's capable of, er,</i> <i> of emotional expressivity.</i>
<I>的自我意识和，嗯，</ I>
<i> And, um, of self-awareness.</i>
发展强大的努力人工智能
The effort to develop a strong artificial intelligence
导致了显著进步
has led to significant advancements
在该领域神经工程，中
in the field of neural engineering,
以及我们的理解人类的大脑。
as well as our understanding of the human brain.
不过，虽然一些重点对仍然遥远的梦
But while some focus on the still-distant dream
一个有思想的计算机，中
of a thinking computer,
我相信旅途更重要
I believe the journey to be more important
比目的。
than the destination.
我的首要任务是用
My priority is to use
我的同事“意外的见解
my colleagues' accidental insights
制定新的方法早期发现的癌症。
to develop new methods for the early detection of cancer.
而在寻找的希望一种治疗老年痴呆症。
And in the hopes of finding a cure for Alzheimer's.
简单地说，拯救生命。
Simply put, to save lives.
[鼓掌]
[ Applause ]
伊夫林：“一种新型的思考是必不可少的，
Evelyn: "A new type of thinking is essential,
如果人类要生存下去并走向更高层次。“
if mankind is to survive and move toward higher levels."
爱因斯坦说，超过50年前。
Albert Einstein said that more than 50 years ago.
并且它不能更相关比它是今天。
And it couldn't be more relevant than it is today.
智能机很快就会允许我们
Intelligent machines will soon allow us
征服我们最棘手的挑战。
to conquer our most intractable challenges.
不仅要治好病，但要消除贫困和饥饿。
Not merely to cure disease, but to end poverty and hunger.
为了医治地球。
To heal the planet.
并建立一个更美好的未来对我们所有人来说。
And build a better future for all of us.
我不知道任何人谁在做多
I don't know anybody who is doing more
让未来成为现实比我们的下一位发言者。
to make that future a reality than our next speaker.
但话又说回来，我可能失之偏颇。
But then again, I'm probably biased.
[笑]
[ Laughter ]
请欢迎我的伙伴在科学和生活。
Please welcome my partner in science and in life.
医生将施法者。
Doctor will caster.
[欢呼和掌声]
[ Cheers and applause ]
请问：非常感谢。
Will: Thank you very much.
我的妻子一直渴望改变世界。
My wife has always been eager to change the world.
但我就定居对于第一次认识它。
But I'll just settle for understanding it first.
[轻笑声]
[ Light laughter ]
对于百和3万年，
For one hundred and thirty thousand years,
我们的理性能力一直没有改变。
our capacity for reason has remained unchanged.
合并智力在神经科学家，
The combined intellect of the neuroscientists,
工程师，数学家和黑客...
engineers, mathematicians and hackers...
[笑]
[ Laughter ]
...在这个礼堂
...in this auditorium
相比简直是小巫见大巫到连最基本的活性成分
pales in comparison to even the most basic a.I.
一旦网上有感觉力的机器
Once online a sentient machine
会很快克服的限制生物学。
will quickly overcome the limits of biology.
并在很短的时间，
And in a short time,
它的分析能力将更大
its analytical power will be greater
比集体智慧
than the collective intelligence
出生的每个人在世界的历史。
of every person born in the history of the world.
[手机铃声]
[ Phone ringing ]
所以，现在想象这样一个实体
So now imagine such an entity
全方位人类的情感。
with a full range of human emotion.
即使是自我意识。
Even self-awareness.
一些科学家参阅本作为“奇点”。
Some scientists refer to this as "the singularity."
我把它称为“超越”。
I call it "transcendence."
路径建设这样的超级智能
The path to building such a super-intelligence
要求我们解开最根本的秘密
requires us to unlock the most fundamental secrets
宇宙。
of the universe.
是什么性质意识？
What is the nature of consciousness?
[平直线]
[ Flatline ]
有没有灵魂？
Is there a soul?
[猴子尖叫声]
[ Monkey screeches ]
如果是的话，它在哪里居住？
And if so, where does it reside?
男人：医生施法者？
Man: Doctor caster?
是的，先生？你有问题吗？
Yes, sir? You have a question?
所以，你想创建一个神呢？
So you wanna create a God?
你自己的上帝？
Your own God?
这是一个非常好的问题。
That's a very good question.
嗯，这不正是男人一直做了什么？
Um, isn't that what man has always done?
医生？
Doctor?
最大：哦，这是无情的！
Max: Oh, it's relentless
谢谢。
Thank you.
你看，现在他的，现在他的假装他不喜欢它。
Look, and now he's, now he's pretending he's not enjoying it.
Yabber yabber yabber。
Yabber yabber yabber.
医生施法者。快感。
Doctor caster. Pleasure.
谢谢。
Thank you.
教授？
Professor?
[枪击，所有的尖叫]
[ Gunshot, all screaming ]
你所有的奴隶！
You're all slaves
[枪击]
[ Gunshot ]
女：<I>小时前，</ I><I>这一设施遭到袭击。</ I>
Woman:<i> Hours ago,</i> <i> this facility was attacked.</i>
<I>我们现在可以确认，至少</ I><I>五人都死了。</ I>
<i> We can now confirm at least</i> <i> five people are dead.</i>
<I> 12人</ I><I>受伤。</ I>
<i> Twelve people</i> <i> have been injured.</i>
<I>此事件涉及</ I>
<i> This incident is related</i>
的<i>一系列</ I>同时攻击的<I> </ I>
<i> to a series</i> <i> of simultaneous attacks</i>
<I>，今天发生的</ I><I>在纽约市，</ I>
<i> that took place today</i> <i> in New York City,</i>
<I>洛杉矶，芝加哥</ I><I>和华盛顿特区，</ I>
<i> Los Angeles, Chicago</i> <i> and Washington, D.C.,</i>
<I>所有这些目标主要</ I><I>电脑和研究实验室</ I>
<i> all of them targeting major</i> <i> computer and research labs</i>
<I>在先进</ I>现场<I>人工智能。</ I>
<i> in the field of advanced</i> <i> artificial intelligence.</i>
<I>到目前为止，没有人声称</ I><I>责任。</ I>
<i> So far no one has claimed</i> <i> responsibility.</i>
马克斯：不，他是正常的。他很幸运。
Max: No, he's alright. He was very lucky.
子弹只是擦伤了他。是啊。好。照顾自己。
The bullet only grazed him. Yup. Okay. Take care.
他们打A.I.实验室全国各地。
They hit a.I. Labs all over the country.
汤姆·凯西的死。
Tom Casey's dead.
他们拿出约瑟的在利弗莫尔的整个团队。
And they took out Joseph's entire team at livermore.
怎么样约瑟夫？
What about Joseph?
他是正常的。
He's alright.
实际上，他是在你的办公室与FBI。
Actually, he's at your office with the FBI.
[警察无线电聊天]
[ Police radio chatter ]
约瑟夫。
Joseph.
最大。
Max.
我的上帝，意志。
My God, will.
你忘了教我们
You forgot to teach us
如何躲避子弹，不是吗？
how to dodge a bullet, didn't you?
他们怎么连进去您的实验室？
How did they even get inside your lab?
我的一个程序员。
One of my programmers.
所有的安全他大摇大摆在
All that security and he waltzes in
与中毒蛋糕。
with a poisoned cake.
二恶英，我们认为。
Dioxin, we think.
呵呵。这是代理布坎南与FBI。
Oh. This is agent Buchanan with the FBI.
嘿。你好
Hey. How do you do?
你好。 [叹气]
Hi. [ Sighs ]
我一直在关注你的研究，医生施法者。
I've been following your research, doctor caster.
这是令人着迷。
It's fascinating.
代理布坎南是的亲密伙伴
Agent Buchanan is a close partner
在我的网络防御工作在利弗莫尔。
in my cyber-defense work at livermore.
嗯，有没有什么地方在那里，我们都可以谈谈吗？
Um, is there somewhere where we can all talk?
可以去我的办公室。刚刚到这里。
Could go to my office. Just down here.
大。
Great.
布坎南：革命独立于技术。
Buchanan: Revolutionary independence from technology.
裂痕。
Rift.
所以，直到两年前，它是所有关于断开连接。
So, till two years ago, it was all about the disconnect.
发短信的人，而不是实际上互相交谈。
People texting instead of actually talking to each other.
社交媒体作为侵犯隐私权。
Social media as an invasion of privacy.
他们做了什么大不了的推杆智能手机在搅拌机。
They made a big deal of putting smartphones in blenders.
但我怕我们都错过了真正的威胁。
But I'm afraid we all missed the real threat.
是啊。这家伙，乔尔·埃德蒙，和我在一起了一年。
Yeah. This guy, Joel Edmund, was with me for a year.
谁拍的意志的人是工作在校园自八月。
The guy who shot will was working on campus since August.
他们渗透他们的目标
They infiltrated their targets
然后协调他们的攻击。
and then coordinated their attacks.
这是疯了。
That's insane.
布坎南：一个小时前，
Buchanan: An hour ago,
他们声称谋杀并发布了自己的宣言。
they claimed the murders and released their manifesto.
“人工智能是一种不自然的憎恶
"Artificial intelligence is an unnatural abomination
和对人类??的威胁。“
and a threat to humanity."
他们决心阻止任何企图
They're determined to stop any attempt
在你叫什么“超越者”。
at what you call "transcendence."
最大：因此，这不是结束了吗？
Max: So this isn't over?
其实，这就是为什么我在这里。
Actually, that's why I'm here.
我们失去了几十年的研究而发展到今天。
We lost decades of research and development today.
对于现在，意志，
For right now, will,
您的实验室是唯一一个这可以唤醒一个强大的活性成分
your lab is the only one that can wake up a strong a.I.
因此，国防部在问 -
So the defense department is asking --
不，不，不，不。坑上，等待。没有，有，无。
no, no, no, no. Hang on, wait. No, there's, no.
我不会让政府英寸
I'm not letting the government in.
我们从来没有采取他们的钱??。号不，不会。
We've never taken their money. No. No, will.
他们只是想知道如果工作步入正轨。
They just want to know if the work is on track.
这一点很重要我们所有人。
It's important to all of us.
布坎南：我们已经听说了很多关于PINN项目，
Buchanan: We've heard a lot about the pinn project,
医生施法者。
doctor caster.
在那里，有什么办法我们能看看吗？
Is there, is there any way we could have a look?
我有选择吗？
Do I have a choice?
是的，当然，你这样做。
Yes, of course, you do.
因此，这些都是国家的最先进的量子处理器。
So these are state-of-the-art quantum processors.
你不会找到更快的计算能力
You won't find faster computational power
其他地方在世界上。
anywhere else in the world.
它看见老教师的图片你。
It's seen old faculty pictures of you.
<I>晚上好，唐纳德·布坎南。</ I>
<i> Good evening, Donald Buchanan.</i>
PINN：<I>晚上好，</ I><I>医生恶搞。</ I>
Pinn:<i> Good evening,</i> <i> doctor tagger.</i>
它知道我吗？
It knows me?
那是当然的。
Of course it does.
DMV记录。社交媒体。
Dmv records. Social media.
PINN，告诉剂布坎南关于你自己。
Pinn, tell agent Buchanan about yourself.
<I>我PINN，</ I>
<i> I am pinn,</i>
<I>一个物理上独立的</ I><I>神经网络</ I>
<i> a physically independent</i> <i> neural network</i>
<I>由医生发明了将施法者。</ I>
<i>invented by doctor will caster.</i>
你能证明你是自我意识？
Can you prove that you are self-aware?
<I>这是一个很难回答的问题，</ I><I>博士恶搞。</ I>
<i> That's a difficult question,</i> <i> Dr. tagger.</i>
<I>你能证明</ i>，您的<i>是？</ I>
<i> Can you prove that</i> you<i> are?</i>
您不能设定一台机器是自我意识，
You can't program a machine to be self-aware,
因为我们不知道如何我们自己的意识的工作。
because we have no idea how our own consciousness works.
这是你的意见。
That is your opinion.
你只是碰巧是错误的。
You just happen to be wrong.
显然，凯西管理要解决这一困境。
Evidently, Casey managed to solve that dilemma.
他给我们送来了他的研究就在他被杀害了。
He sent us his research just before he was killed.
后马上收拾行装，我们会送过来吧。
Soon as it's packed up, we'll send it over.
我想你会发现我们将帮助合作伙伴，
I think you'll find we'll be helpful partners,
医生施法者。
doctor caster.
你没事吧，会吗？
You alright, will?
不，他需要休息。我想我们在这里完成。
No, he needs rest. I think we're done here.
[曼波斯]我很抱歉。
[ Mumbles ] I'm so sorry.
没关系。
That's fine.
好。抱歉。
Okay. Sorry.
[威尔咳嗽]
[ Will coughing ]
请问，嘿，嘿！
Will, hey, hey
来吧，坐起来。
Come on, sit up.
坐起来，要小心。
Sit up, be careful.
[气喘吁吁]
[ Panting ]
医生施特劳斯：我们的第一个想到的总是感染。
Doctor Strauss: Our first thought is always infection.
但鉴于当时的情况，我们将扩大搜索范围。
But given the circumstances, we'll widen the search.
我们会想出解决办法。
We'll figure this out.
[设备哔]
[ Device beeping ]
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
这是一个同位素叫钋。
It's an isotope called polonium.
子弹一定是股价与它。
The bullet must have been laced with it.
有它的踪迹在伤口上。
There were traces of it at the wound.
那么，有什么治疗方法？
Well, what's the treatment?
这是辐射中毒。
It's radiation poisoning.
我怕一旦它进入血液，
I'm afraid that once it enters the bloodstream,
效果是不可逆的。
the effect is irreversible.
有了适当的照顾，
With proper care,
我们正在寻找4，也许5周
we're looking at 4, maybe 5 weeks
他的系统之前，关闭。
before his system shuts down.
[流淌着诗情画意]
[ Sniffles ]
[声音打破]我就在这里。
[ Voice breaking ] I'm right here.
请问：它只是没有任何意义。
Will: It just doesn't make sense.
他们害怕技术
They're afraid of technology
由于它的威胁人性化。
because of its threat to humanity.
然而，他们不退缩在服用了生命。
Yet they don't flinch at taking a life.
所以，很显然他们没有大的逻辑。
So obviously they're not big on logic.
但有没有短缺的讽刺。
But there's no shortage of irony.
人最怕什么他们不明白。
People fear what they don't understand.
他们总是有。
They always have.
约瑟就打发了凯西的文件。
Joseph sent over Casey's files.
他被解码的突触在实时。
He was decoding the synapses in real time.
但正确的输入算法...
But with the right input algorithms...
我需要找回到实验室。
I need to get back to the lab.
将...
Will...
是真的你想怎么花
Is that really how you wanna spend
上个月你的生活？
the last month of your life?
[软，古典音乐剧]
[ Soft, classical music plays ]
嘿，你在干什么？
Hey, what are you doing?
我想拥有这一切带回办公室
I want to have all this taken back to the office
告诉约瑟夫...
to tell Joseph...
我已经花了我的整个生命在计算机实验室。
That I've spent my entire life in a computer lab.
我决定，我宁愿花它与你的休息。
I decided I'd rather spend the rest of it with you.
[鸟儿的鸣叫]
[ Birds chirping ]
[叹气]
[ Sighing ]
约瑟夫：伊夫林？你还好吗？
Joseph: Evelyn? Are you okay?
是啊。是的，我想。
Yeah. Yeah, I suppose.
你看，他不能工作了。
Look, he can't work anymore.
我们要去将它关闭。
We're gonna shut it down.
我只是想让你知道。
I just wanted you to know.
当然。
Of course.
好了，不用担心PINN。
Well, don't worry about pinn.
就拿意志的照顾。
Take care of will.
并照顾好自己。
And take care of yourself.
谢谢你，乔。
Thanks, Joe.
您需要什么，我在这里，好吗？
Anything you need, I'm here, okay?
[聊天]
[ Chatter ]
[钥匙叮当]
[ Keys jingle ]
[键盘会发出蜂鸣声]
[ Keypad beeps ]
[蜂鸣器]
[ Buzzer ]
[键盘嗑]
[ Keyboard clacking ]
伊夫林：你看，这一切都建立销凯西的解决方案
Evelyn: Look, it's all built off of Casey's solution
到自我意识问题。
to the self-awareness problem.
他半年前做了。
He did it six months ago.
他做了什么呢？
He did what exactly?
而不是创建一个的人工智能，
Instead of creating an artificial intelligence,
他重复现有的1。
he duplicated an existing one.
告诉我，你是在开玩笑。
Tell me you're joking.
他记录了猴子的大脑活动
He recorded the monkey's brain activity
并上载其意识喜欢的一首歌或电影。
and uploaded its consciousness like a song or a movie.
你出你的心灵。
You're out of your mind.
将身体快不行了，
Will's body is dying,
但他心中是一个模式的电信号
but his mind is a pattern of electrical signals
我们可以上传到PINN。
that we can upload into pinn.
他可以，他可以陈德良 - 电动车，他不是一只猴子！
He can, he can tran-- ev, he's not a monkey
假设植入电极进入他的大脑
Assuming that implanting an electrode into his brain
实际上并没有杀他而这个作品，
doesn't actually kill him and that this works,
在最好的
at the very best
你会做一个数字逼近他。
you'll be making a digital approximation of him.
如果我们错过了什么，任何事情 -
If we missed anything, anything --
一个念头，一个通道 - 一个童年的记忆 -
a thought, a ch-- a childhood memory --
你怎么会知道你处??理什么用？
how will you know what you're dealing with?
没有人说我们放弃了，
No one is saying that we give up,
但我们应该集中我们的努力纳米技术。
but we should be focusing our efforts on nanotechnology.
合成的血细胞。两者都是几十年的时间。
Synthetic blood cells. Both are decades away.
这就是我们现在有。
This is what we have now.
我们能救他。
We can save him.
看看他们做了什么给他。
Look at what they did to him.
请问：尽管我知道我是一个死人......
Will: Even though I know I'm a dead man...
我很担心，我会想念她的。
I'm worried I'll miss her.
看...
Look...
我将早已不复存在。
I'll be long gone.
但是你，你将永远听不到它的结束...
But you, you'll never hear the end of it...
如果我们不尝试。
If we don't try.
我知道。
I know.
我想认为我是足够聪明，救你。
I'd like to think that I was smart enough to save you.
不要小看你自己。
Don't underestimate yourself.
你是第三个最聪明的人，我知道。
You're the third smartest person I know.
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
[笑]
[ Chuckles ]
[拍手手意志的腿]
[ Claps hand on will's leg ]
你确定吗？
Are you sure about this?
不够好为猴子。
Good enough for the monkey.
嘿。
Hey.
照顾她。
Take care of her.
[呼呼]
[ Whirring ]
嘿。
Hey.
它的工作，宝贝。它的工作。
It worked, baby. It's working.
把凯西个月来排序通过对原始数据。
Took Casey months to sort through the raw data.
他有一整个团队。
And he had an entire team.
他没有我。
He didn't have me.
[呼呼]
[ Whirring ]
请问：隔阻。
Will: Deadening.
致命的。
Deadly.
聋。
Deaf.
震聋。
Deafen.
处理。
Deal.
院长。
Dean.
经销商。
Dealer.
公平的。
Fair.
告别。
Farewell.
不要失去自己此。
Don't lose yourself to this.
LA。
LA.
标签。
Label.
<I>劳动。</ I>
<i> Labor.</i>
<I>迷宫。</ I>
<i> Labyrinth.</i>
<I>花边。</ I>
<i> Lace.</i>
试着多一点。
Try a little more.
来吧。只是多一个。继续下去。
Come on. Just one more. Go on.
[拥吻]
[ Smooches ]
谢谢。
Thank you.
[手机剧上升笔记]
[ Phone plays ascending notes ]
好吧，意志，是时候为你的药丸。
Okay, will, it's time for your pill.
会，醒了。
Will, wake up.
醒来。
Wake up.
[呜咽]
[ Sobs ]
约瑟夫：“我亲爱的伊夫林...
Joseph: "My dear Evelyn...
“我不知道该如何表达悲伤
"I don't know how to express the sadness
“我觉得你的损失。
"I feel for your loss.
“对于我们的<i> </ i>的损失。
"For<i> our</i> loss.
“你要知道，要意志...
"You must know that to will...
“你是所有是有史以来要紧。
"You were all that ever mattered.
“你的爱和伙伴关系
"Your love and partnership
“是那种我们其余的人只能梦想的。
"was the kind the rest of us can only dream of.
“我们失去了一位伟大的头脑。
"We lost a great mind.
“一个伟大的灵魂。
"A great soul.
这名男子的“圣灵
"But the spirit of this man
将继续激励我们。“
will continue to inspire us."
刚刚得到消息。
Just got word.
PINN的关闭。
Pinn's shut down.
但是，呃，显然几核心的缺失。
But, uh, apparently a few of the cores are missing.
我用尽了一切。
I've tried everything.
语言处理，密码学。
Language processing, cryptography.
编码。
Coding.
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
我无法弄清楚。
I can't figure it out.
我想是错误的。
I wanted to be wrong.
是啊。
Yeah.
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
好，只是让我说再见。
Okay, just let me say goodbye.
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
我不知道如果你能听到我。
I don't know if you can hear me.
也许你可以。
Maybe you can.
你说“不要失去自己。”
You said "don't lose yourself."
所以，我，嗯，嗯......
So I, uh, hmm...
我要听你的。
I'm going to listen to you.
[声音打破]好吧。[叹气]
[ Voice breaking ] Okay. [ Sighs ]
只是把它关掉，将其关闭。
Just turn it off, turn it off.
[系统关闭]
[ System shuts down ]
好。
Okay.
等待。
Wait.
我们需要擦拭驱动器。
We need to wipe the drives.
坚持，稍等。 [叹气]
Hold on. [ Sighs ]
等等，等等。
Wait, wait.
[键盘嗑]神。
[ Keyboard clacking ] God.
[深呼吸]
[ Breathes deeply ]
[喘息，笑]
[ Gasps, laughs ]
[流淌着诗情画意]
[ Sniffles ]
[笑气喘吁吁]
[ Chuckles breathlessly ]
[流淌着诗情画意]嗯，嗯。
[ Sniffles ] Uh, uh.
你能听到我吗？
Can you hear me?
[<I>会讲</ I><I>隐约</ I>]
[<i> Will speaking</i> <i> indistinctly</i> ]
<I>我，我可以的。</ I>
<i> I, I can.</i>
请问，我的上帝。
Will, my God.
<I>这是黑暗的。</ I>
<i> It's dark.</i>
他什么都看不到。
He can't see anything.
相机。
The camera.
[<I>说起隐约</ I>]
[<i> Speaking indistinctly</i> ]
那里。你可以，你现在可以看到我吗？
There. Can you, can you see me now?
[<I>说起隐约</ I>]
[<i> Speaking indistinctly</i> ]
<I>伊夫林。</ I>
<i> Evelyn.</i>
我在这里。
I'm here.
的<i>我有</ i>的唯一的恐惧<I>在生活中是损失... </ I>
<i> The only fear that I have</i> <i> in life is the loss...</i>
<I>如果发生这种情况，</ I><I>当它发生... </ I>
<i> If it were to happen,</i> <i> when it does happen...</i>
[<I>说起隐约</ I>]
[<i> Speaking indistinctly</i> ]
<I> ...最后一刻。</ I>
<i> ...last moment.</i>
<I>上次你看</ I><I>在这双眼睛。</ I>
<i> Last time you look</i> <i> in those eyes.</i>
的<i>这一目标的可能性... </ I>
<i> The possibility of that end...</i>
[<I>说起隐约</ I>]
[<i> Speaking indistinctly</i> ]
<I>我想念你这么多。</ I>
<i> I miss you so much.</i>
<I>黑暗。</ I>
<i> Dark.</i>
<I>我记得痛</ I>
<i> I remember the pain</i>
<I>，我不记得</ I>的<i>就是我想说的。</ I>
<i> and I can't remember</i> <i> what I want to say.</i>
<I>这就像</ I><I>从梦中醒来。</ I>
<i> It was like</i> <i> waking from a dream.</i>
<I>这确实是令人难以置信的。</ I>
<i> It was truly incredible.</i>
<I>我从来没有觉得</ I><I>这样的事。</ I>
<i> I've never felt</i> <i> anything like this.</i>
<I>我没想到</ I><I>我可能是这个样子。</ I>
<i> I didn't think</i> <i> I could be like this.</i>
<I>思想是有</ I><I>但他们不... </ I>
<i> Thoughts are there</i> <i> but they don't...</i>
会吗？
Will?
<I> ...到达正确。</ I>
<i> ...arrive properly.</i>
我认为他仍然支离破碎。
I think he's still fragmented.
我要去执行诊断。
I'm gonna run a diagnostic.
[流淌着诗情画意]
[ Sniffles ]
伊夫林。
Evelyn.
哦，我的上帝，他重新安排了自己的代码。
Oh, my God, he's reordering his own code.
[喘息]这是不可思议的。
[ Gasps ] It's incredible.
我们怎么知道这其实是他吗？
How do we know this is actually him?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我们建立了这个从PINN的核心。
We built this from pinn's core.
我们不知道有多少
We don't know how much
意志的意识居然活了下来。
of will's consciousness actually survived.
[笑]
[ Chuckles ]
<I>我会需要扩大。</ I><I>我需要更多的力量。</ I>
<i> I'm gonna need to expand.</i> <i> I need more power.</i>
<I>新处理器</ I><I>三倍多能干</ I>
<i> New processor</i> <i> three times more capable</i>
<I>这比目前的系统。</ I>
<i> than this current system.</i>
<I>这些设计。</ I><I>我简直不敢之前看到它。</ I>
<i> These designs.</i> <i> I just couldn't see it before.</i>
<I>我无法描述它。</ I>
<i> I can't describe it.</i>
<I>这就像我的心</ I><I>已经被释放。</ I>
<i> It's like my mind</i> <i> has been set free.</i>
<I>你应该给我上线。</ I>
<i> You need to get me online.</i>
<I>我需要访问</ I><I>金融市场，</ I>
<i> I need to access</i> <i> financial markets,</i>
<I>教育资料库... </ I>
<i> educational databases...</i>
马克斯，你可以想像他希望有能力的，
Max, can you imagine what he'd be capable of,
如果联网了他？
if we networked him?
不，你没有。你在干什么？
No, you, no. What are you doing?
马克斯，他不能看到或听到。
Max, he can't see or hear.
我重新连接他。
I'm reconnecting him.
这不是他的。它不是。
It's not him. It's not.
这可能是聪明的，甚至可能是有知觉的，
It may be intelligent, may even be sentient,
但这不是意志。
but this is not will.
十五分钟它打开后，
Fifteen minutes after it turns on,
它要插到了华尔街？
it wants to plug into wall street?
获得更快？更厉害？
Get faster? More powerful?
这听起来像意志给你？
Does that sound like will to you?
你如何解释这些图片？
How do you explain these images?
股票镜头。PINN可能已经访问了它们
Stock footage. Pinn could have accessed them
从芯中的任何一个我们从实验室拿了。
from any one of the cores we took from the lab.
不，不是这样。这就是富翁公园。
No, not that. That's nabob park.
会带我去在我们的第一次约会。
Will took me there on our first date.
我说我喜欢旋转木马音乐，拉格泰姆一些调整。号
I said that I liked the carousel music, some ragtime tune. No.
第二天，他出现在我家
The next day, he shows up at my house
与老唱机。
with that old record player.
号最大，这些都是回忆。
No. Max, these are memories.
他们是真正的。他们不是 - 坚持，稍等。
They're real. They're not -- hold on.
他们不是一些股票视频从某些硬盘驱动器。
They're not some stock video from some hard drive.
只是听。这是他！
Just listen. It's him
好吧。所有我问的是我们很小心。
Alright. All I'm asking is that we're careful.
我们将它关闭，直到我们知道我们正在处理。
We shut it down until we know what we're dealing with.
关闭它？它关闭！
Shut it down? Shut it down
它的意志！
It's will
出去！我不能这样做。
Get out I can't do that.
出去！
Get out
你怎么可以这样说？
How can you say that?
出去。
Get out.
[<I>会讲</ I><I>隐约</ I>]
[<i> Will speaking</i> <i> indistinctly</i> ]
<I>伊夫林？</ I>
<i> Evelyn?</i>
<I>哪里最大？</ I>
<i> Where's Max?</i>
他必须去。
He had to go.
<i>最高是迷茫的，是不是他？</ I>
<i> Max is confused, isn't he?</i>
他是担心。
He's concerned.
<I>您是否担心？</ I>
<i> Are you concerned?</i>
[笑]
[ Laughs ]
号
No.
[似有似无的对话]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
医生水域？
Doctor waters?
我能和你谈谈？
Can I talk to you?
你知道吗？这是小时后。
You know what? It's after hours.
你为什么不叫我的办公室？
Why don't you call my office?
设立预约。
Set up an appointment.
布雷。
Bree.
我是学生你的工作。
I'm a student of your work.
崇拜者，真的。
An admirer, really.
你搏斗的方式与张力
The way you wrestle with the tension
技术的承诺之间其后果自负。
between technology's promise and its peril.
科学的大多数男人如果忽视它。
Most men of science are blind to it.
到底是什么你想要什么？
What exactly is it you want?
只是一些清晰度。
Just some clarity.
我知道这是困难的。
I know it's difficult.
大多数你的同事
Most of your colleagues
和一些你最亲密的朋友。
and some of your closest friends.
他们不知道的危险。
They don't know the danger.
写论文是一回事。
Writing a paper is one thing.
我想知道是什么在你的心脏。
I'm wondering what's in your heart.
我不知道是怎么回事你找到了我，
I don't know how it is you found me,
但不管它是你想要的，我对此不感兴趣。
but whatever it is you want, I'm not interested.
对不起/打扰一下。这是很重要的。
Excuse me. This is important.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
[叫声]
[ Grunting ]
[发动机翻身]
[ Engine turns over ]
[轮胎发出刺耳的声音]
[ Tires screech ]
[门打开]
[ Door opens ]
[拍击]
[ Rattling ]
布雷：告诉我关于伊夫林施法者。
Bree: Tell me about Evelyn caster.
我们知道她拿该PINN芯
We know she took the pinn cores
我们知道关于凯西的文件。
and we know about Casey's files.
我们知道你正在构建的。
We know what you're building.
鲍勃：你不明白这一点，你呢？
Bob: You don't get it, do you?
她连接了到互联网，
She connects it to the Internet,
它会做的第一件事是自我复制
the first thing it'll do is copy itself
到每一个联网计算机在世界
onto every single networked computer in the world
再有就是没有把它下来。
and then there is no taking it down.
她在哪里？
Where is she?
乔尔：“危险，我们面临是未来
Joel: "The danger we face is a future
“那里的医生都是技术人员，不是医生。
"where doctors are technicians, not physicians.
“机器是为了帮助人的心灵，
"Machines are meant to aid the human mind,
而不是取代它。“
not supplant it."
他们是你的话。
They're your words.
你想救她或不？
You wanna save her or not?
我们有她的位置。4550圣巴勃罗。
We have her location. 4550 San Pablo.
我们走吧。嘿！嘿！
Let's go. Hey
我们走吧！嘿，不要碰她！
Let's go Hey, don't touch her
你听到了吗？！不要碰她！
Do you hear me? Don't touch her
[蟋蟀的鸣叫]
[ Crickets chirping ]
[光哔]
[ Light beeping ]
伊夫林：妈的！
Evelyn: Shit
我一定要得到你现在在线。
I have to get you online now.
你可以看到卫星软件？
Can you see the satellite software?
<I>我看到它。</ I><I>我现在安装它。</ I>
<i> I see it.</i> <i> I'm installing it now.</i>
[玻璃打碎]
[ Glass shatters ]
[钻]
[ Drilling ]
我们来得太晚了。
We're too late.
[枪声]
[ Gunshots ]
[乱码的声音]
[ Garbled voices ]
[铃声播放]
[ Ringtone plays ]
[深呼吸]
[ Breathes deeply ]
[呼气大幅]
[ Exhales sharply ]
会吗？
Will?
<I>我很好，伊夫林。</ I><I>我在线上。</ I>
<i> I'm fine, Evelyn.</i> <i> I'm online.</i>
好。
Okay.
<I>让我们给你</ I><I>某处安全。</ I>
<i> Let's get you</i> <i> someplace safe.</i>
[似有似无的对话]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
<I>我需要你在这里等。</ I>
<i> I need you to wait here.</i>
什么？你要去哪里？
What? Where are you going?
<I>无处不在。</ I>
<i> Everywhere.</i>
<I>你不能留在这儿，伊夫林。</ I>
<i> You can't stay here, Evelyn.</i>
<I>你不能回家。</ I>
<i> You can't go home.</i>
你是什??么意思？我在哪里要去？
What do you mean? Where am I gonna go?
<I>我采取的是照顾。</ I>
<i> I'm taking care of that.</i>
好。
Okay.
嗨，我，嗯，有一个预约根据“图灵，”我想。
Hi, I, uh, have a reservation under "turing," I think.
[键盘噼啪声]
[ Keyboard clacks ]
[猛击]
[ Banging ]
一家名为全球金融相交
A company called global intersecting finance
只是做三千八百万美元
just made thirty-eight million dollars
从大批量交易过过去24小时。
from high-volume trading over the past twenty-four hours.
全资拥有的一家公司伊夫林施法者。
A company fully owned by Evelyn caster.
哪里是伊夫林？
Where's Evelyn?
你做了什么她？
What have you done with her?
我们都为时已晚。
We were too late.
它的存在了。
It's out there now.
她还活着？
Is she alive?
你知道的源代码，最大。
You know the source code, Max.
你可以帮使这一权利。
You can help make this right.
使这个权利？
Make this right?
它是什么你在想什么？
What is it you're thinking?
那我会帮你呢？
That I'm gonna help you?
那你会招我吗？
That you're gonna recruit me?
自己决定。
Decide for yourself.
布坎南：在这里。布雷文斯杜克大学就读计算机科学。
Buchanan: Here. Bree nevins attended Duke computer sciences.
实习2009年凯西。
Interned for Casey 2009.
她加入了一个激进新卢德派集团2010年。
She joined a radical Neo-luddite group 2010.
我猜会发生裂痕几年以后。
I guess rift happens a couple of years later.
现在，电子邮件 -
Now, the emails --
男人：这是怎么回事？我越来越多个屏
man: What's going on? I'm getting multiple screens.
乔，在手机上获得。谁？我们已经被黑客入侵。
Joe, get on the phone. Anybody? We've been hacked.
有谁知道这哪里是哪里来的？
Does anyone know where this is coming from?
等等，刚刚发生了什么？是啊，我们这里有一个问题。
Wait, what just happened? Yeah, we got a problem here.
我与特区它不只是我们。
I'm on with D.C. it's not just us.
每场办事处一直打到。
Every field office has been hit.
好吧，请告诉我我们正在追查这一点。
Okay, please tell me we're tracing this.
我想，但传入查询所有匿名。
I'm trying, but the incoming queries are all anonymized.
约瑟夫：你不被黑客攻击。
Joseph: You're not being hacked.
你被帮助。
You're being helped.
请问：<I>我访问监控</ I><I>摄像头遍布全国。</ I>
Will:<i> I've accessed surveillance</i> <i> cameras all over the country.</i>
<I>他们将有大部分</ I><I>在押明天。</ I>
<i> They'll have most of them</i> <i> in custody by tomorrow.</i>
<I>我们不能呆在这里，伊夫林。</ I>
<i> We can't stay here, Evelyn.</i>
<I>我们需要下车的网格。</ I>
<i> We need to get off the grid.</i>
访问数千数据库？
Accessing thousands of databases?
地理定位嫌疑人实时？
Geo-locating suspects in real time?
我从来没有见过这样的事情。
I've never seen anything like it.
也许除了从PINN。
Except maybe from pinn.
[叹气]好吧。
[ Sighs ] Okay.
你去哪儿？
Where you going?
取下一个恐怖组织。
Taking down a terrorist organization.
你的工作在PINN角度。
You work on the pinn angle.
当你看着办吧，你让我知道该感谢谁了。
When you figure it out, you let me know who to thank.
你背后的双手！女：啊哈！
Hands behind your back Woman: Aah
鲍勃：波士顿，费城，纽约。
Bob: Boston, Philly, New York.
我们搞砸。
We're screwed.
我们为此做好了准备。
We prepared for this.
<I>镇被称为</ I><I>亮木。</ I>
<i> The town is called</i> <i> brightwood.</i>
<I>看起来不像了。</ I>
<i> Doesn't look like much.</i>
<I>但它是一个完美的地方</ I>的<i>建设。</ I>
<i> But it's the perfect place</i> <i> to build.</i>
我不明白这一点。
I don't get it.
<I>我认为我们有机会</ I>的<i>在这里做伟大的事情。</ I>
<i> I think we have an opportunity</i> <i> to do great things here.</i>
[期刊论文沙沙]
[ Papers rustle ]
所以，一个地下数据中心。
So, an underground data center.
而你要我改造几乎每一个结构的位置。
And you want me to renovate nearly every structure in town.
嗯。
Mm-hm.
我有六个人在我的船员。
I've got six guys on my crew.
雇用更多。
Hire more.
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
你看，夫人，在所有诚实，亮木是一个转储。
Look, ma'am, in all honesty, brightwood's a dump.
我什至不知道你为什么想要在这里浪费你的钱。
I'm not even sure why you want to waste your money here.
你确定你有正确的小镇？
You sure you got the right town?
事情是，马丁，
Thing is, Martin,
我和老公已经购买的土地。
my husband and I have already purchased the land.
我们购买了家园。我们购买了酒店。
We purchased the homes. We purchased the hotel.
而到了时间你和我完成谈话，
And by the time you and I are done talking,
我们将自己的这个小餐馆。
we'll own this diner.
我们住。
We're staying.
我们希望您为我们工作。
We would like you to work for us.
并没有一个数字可以报价我们，太大了。
And there isn't a number you can quote us that's too big.
[清喉]好。
[ Clears throat ] Okay.
[不明显的谈话]
[ Indistinct conversation ]
鲍勃：手机。
Bob: Cell phones.
你知道，我，我以前的工作托马斯凯西。
You know, I, I used to work for Thomas Casey.
我实习的他。
I interned for him.
一天晚上，他邀请我们所有在到实验室，
One night, he invites us all over to the lab,
为我们提供了这整个演讲关于历史，
gives us this whole speech about history,
在发放香槟，就像他刚刚治愈癌症。
hands out champagne, like he just cured cancer.
而且你知道，
And you know,
当他上传那猕猴，
when he uploaded that rhesus monkey,
我其实是幸福的他。
I was actually happy for him.
我们所有的人。
We all were.
然后我意识到
And then I realized
我们已经越过一条线。
we had crossed a line.
该机器还以为是猴子从来没有吸了口气。
The machine that thought it was a monkey never took a breath.
它从来没有吃过，从来没有睡过。
It never ate, never slept.
它只是尖叫。
It just screamed.
有人乞讨让我们停下来。
It was begging for us to stop.
将其关闭。
To shut it down.
一小群人会得到一起谈话。
A small group of us would get together and talk.
主要是关于你的哲学。
Mostly about your philosophy.
和你的顾虑。
And your concerns.
我想你应该知道。
I thought you should know.
[水龙头门]
[ Taps door ]
[门打开]
[ Door opens ]
[门关闭】
[ Door closes ]
[似有似无的对话]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
什么？
What?
PINN永远无法区分之间的对与错。
Pinn could never distinguish between right and wrong.
证明忠诚，对不对？
Demonstrate loyalty, right?
Casey的问题的解决方案：自我意识
Casey's solution to the problem of self-awareness:
使用现有的头脑。
Use an existing mind.
号
No.
<I>所以，你想创建一个神呢？</ I>
<i> So you wanna create a God?</i>
的<i>你自己的上帝？</ I>
<i> Your own God?</i>
请问：<I>这是一个非常好的问题。</ I>
Will: <i> That's a very good question.</i>
<I>嗯，这不正是人</ I><I>一直做？</ I>
<i> Um, isn't that what man</i> <i> has always done?</i>
[似有似无的对话]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
他们正在建设一些大在那里。
They're building something big out there.
布雷：什么是它做出来呢？
Bree: What's it doing out there?
它需要成长。
It needs to grow.
为了推进。
To advance.
现在，它的解决地方它认为它是安全的
Right now, it's settling somewhere it thinks it's safe
来自外部的威胁。
from outside threats.
但它会多要。
But it will want more than that.
一段时间后生存是不够的。
After a while survival won't be enough.
这将扩大，演变，
It will expand, evolve,
影响...
influence...
也许是整个世界。
Perhaps the entire world.
夫人脚轮？
Mrs. caster?
一个和两个处于联机状态。
One and two are online.
六，七将于明天。
Six and seven will be on tomorrow.
布雷：那么我们该如何阻止它？
Bree: So how do we stop it?
你不能。
You can't.
不是所有的孤独。
Not all alone.
现在不是。
And not now.
等待它走的太远。
Wait for it to go too far.
等待的人醒来。
Wait for people to wake up.
号
No.
我们没有时间等待。
We don't have time to wait.
我们必须靠拢。
We have to move closer.
[<I>约玛·kaukonen的“创世纪”</ I><I>播放</ I>]
[<i> Jorma kaukonen's "genesis"</i> <i> plays</i> ]
请问：的<i>欢迎回家</ I>。
Will:<i> Welcome home.</i>
?<I>的时机已经到来</ I>的<i>我们暂停</ I>?
?<i> The time has come</i> <i> for us to pause</i> ?
[伊夫林笑]
[ Evelyn chuckles ]
?Ⅰ和思考生活</ I><I>因为它是</ I>?
?<i> And think of living</i> <i> as it was</i> ?
?<I>到未来</ I><I>我们必须跨越</ I>?
?<i> into the future</i> <i> we must cross</i> ?
[笑]?<I>必须跨越</ I>?
[ chuckles ] ?<i> must cross</i> ?
?<I>我想去</ I>的<i>与你</ I>?
?<i> and I'd like to go</i> <i> with you</i> ?
是一样的吗？
is that the same?
<I>是啊。</ I>
<i> Yup.</i>
<I>这是相同的。</ I>
<i> It's the same one.</i>
<I>你想</ I>的<i>一杯酒？</ I>
<i> Would you like</i> <i> a glass of wine?</i>
在一分钟内。
In a minute.
?<I>我爱你到极点</ I><I>比他们都</ I>?
?<i> I love you dearer</i> <i> than them all</i> ?
?<I>他们都</ I>?
?<i> them all</i> ?
?<I>所以让我陪着你</ I>?
?<i> so let me stay with you</i> ?
你还记得吗当我们第一次见面？
do you remember when we first met?
<I>我记得一切。</ I>
<i> I remember everything.</i>
<I>你走</ I>的<i>进约瑟的类</ I>
<i> You walked</i> <i> into Joseph's class</i>
<I>周二，</ I><I>四月十六。</ I>
<i> on Tuesday,</i> <i> April sixteenth.</i>
晚上<I>之前下过雨，</ I><I>但那天太阳出来。</ I>
<i> Rained the night before,</i> <i> but that day the sun was out.</i>
<I>约瑟夫说你是</ I><I>我的联赛，</ I>
<i> Joseph said you were</i> <i> out of my league,</i>
<I>但我一直很喜欢</ I>的<i>一个挑战。</ I>
<i> but I always liked</i> <i> a challenge.</i>
<I>你是最美丽的</ I><I>女人，我见过。</ I>
<i> You were the most beautiful</i> <i> woman I'd ever seen.</i>
[雷霆隆隆]
[ Thunder rumbles ]
[针刮]
[ Needle scratching ]
[喘气]
[ Gasping ]
请问：？的<i>你还好吗</ I>
Will:<i> You alright?</i>
[气喘吁吁]
[ Panting ]
是啊。
Yeah.
[气喘吁吁]
[ Panting ]
<I>看看。</ I>
<i> Take a look.</i>
<I>我们已经取得了突破</ I>的<i>与纳米技术。</ I>
<i> We've made a breakthrough</i> <i> with the nanotechnology.</i>
<I>我们可以重建任何材料</ I><I>比以前更快。</ I>
<i> We can rebuild any material</i> <i> faster than before.</i>
<I>人造干细胞，</ I><I>组织再生。</ I>
<i> Synthetic stem cells,</i> <i> tissue regeneration.</i>
的<i>的医疗应用</ I><I>现在是无限的。</ I>
<i> The medical applications</i> <i> are now limitless.</i>
这是非凡的。
It's extraordinary.
<I>他们会在第一次被吓到。</ I>
<i> They'll be scared at first.</i>
<I>但是，一旦他们看到什么</ I><I>的技术可以做到，</ I>
<i> But once they see what</i> <i> the technology can do,</i>
<I>我觉得</ I><I>他们会接受它。</ I>
<i> I think that</i> <i> they will embrace it.</i>
<I>我认为</ I><I>它会改变他们的生活。</ I>
<i> And I think</i> <i> it will change their lives.</i>
[似有似无的对话]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[女电脑语音说话含糊不清]
[ Female computerized voice speaks indistinctly ]
<I>安全代码。</ I>
<i> Security code.</i>
[哔声]
[ Beeping ]
<I>状态。</ I>[沙沙]
<i> Status.</i> [ Rustling ]
[呼吸摇摇晃晃]
[ Breathes shakily ]
吓死我了。
Scared the shit out of me.
抱歉。
Sorry.
德雷克，我知道了！来吧！
Drake, I got it Come on
我拿到了钱。来吧！
I got the money. Come on
[咕噜]
[ Grunts ]
我们走吧！[笑]
Let's go [ Laughs ]
请问：<I>把他放在桌子上，</ I><i>请。</ I>
Will:<i> Put him on the table,</i> <i> please.</i>
伊夫林：在这里。把他放在桌子上。
Evelyn: Here. Put him on the table.
小心，小心。
Careful, careful.
<I>现在退一步。</ I>
<i> Now step back.</i>
退一步。
Step back.
这到底是怎么回事？
What the hell's happening?
<I>这些人应该等待</ I><I>外，伊夫林。</ I>
<i> These men should wait</i> <i> outside, Evelyn.</i>
现在来吧。
Come on now.
等等，还有，你是什么乐队'给他？
Wait, well, what are you doin' to him?
我们正在救他。
We're saving him.
[咕噜]
[ Grunts ]
[重击声]
[ Thuds ]
你不害怕，是你吗？
You're not afraid, are you?
编号：[笑]
No. [ Chuckles ]
我的船员得到了一点点惊吓。
My crew got a little spooked.
嗯......
Well...
你好吗？
How are you?
好。
Better.
[设备发出蜂鸣声]
[ Device beeps ]
请问：的<i>物理增强</ I><I>仅仅是一个开始。</ I>
Will:<i> The physical enhancements</i> <i> are just the start.</i>
你是什??么意思？
What do you mean?
<I>他也连接到我。</ I>
<i> He's also connected to me.</i>
[意志的声音]是我，伊夫林。
[ Will's voice ] It's me, Evelyn.
现在我可以摸你。
I can touch you now.
哦，耶稣。
Oh, Jesus.
伊夫林。
Evelyn.
不，不，N-N-N-N-NO。
No, no, n-n-n-n-no.
我不能。伊夫林...
I can't. Evelyn...
我不能。
I can't.
[鸟的鸣叫]
[ Bird chirping ]
[喘气]
[ Gasping ]
的<i>另一个梦想是什么？</ I>
<i> Another dream?</i>
是啊。是啊。
Yeah. Yeah.
<I>我做了一个突破</ I><I>昨晚。</ I>
<i> I made a breakthrough</i> <i> last night.</i>
<I>我觉得</ I><I>你会很高兴的。</ I>
<i> I think</i> <i> you'll be very pleased.</i>
好。
Okay.
我穿好衣服。
I'll get dressed.
一起来看看。
Take a look.
这是得掂量800磅。
That's gotta weigh eight hundred pounds.
[狗在吠距离]
[ Dog barks in distance ]
[爆裂]
[ Crackling ]
马丁：欢迎光临。
Martin: Welcome.
我们很高兴你在这里。
We're glad you're here.
这都是什么人在这里干什么？
What are all these people doing here?
<I>裂谷发布了一段视频</ I>马丁<I>在线。</ I>
<i> Rift posted a video</i> <i> of Martin online.</i>
<I>它去病毒。</ I>
<i> It went viral.</i>
什么，你的意思你让它去病毒。
What, you mean you let it go viral.
<I>这些人的痛苦，</ I><I>伊夫林。</ I>
<i> These people are suffering,</i> <i> Evelyn.</i>
<I>他们没有希望。</ I>
<i> They have no hope.</i>
Ⅰ和我能够解决这些问题。</ I>
<i> And I'm able to fix them.</i>
<I>但也有其他人</ I><I>谁不明白。</ I>
<i> But there are others</i> <i> who don't understand.</i>
<I>它的时间</ I><I>，大家有目共睹。</ I>
<i> It's time</i> <i> for everybody to see.</i>
代理布坎南。
Agent Buchanan.
医生施法者。
Doctor caster.
约瑟夫。
Joseph.
所以，很高兴见到你，伊芙琳。这么好。
So good to see you, Evelyn. So good.
很高兴见到你了。跟我来。
Good to see you, too. Follow me.
该设施是5层向下
The facility is 5 stories down
这样我们就可以控制在实验室的温度。
so that we can control the temperature in the lab.
<I>欢迎。</ I>
<i> Welcome.</i>
<I>我们很高兴你在这里。</ I>
<i> We're glad you're here.</i>
布坎南：耶稣基督。
Buchanan: Jesus Christ.
会吗？
Will?
<I>你惊讶地看着我，</ I><I>约瑟夫？</ I>
<i> You surprised to see me,</i> <i> Joseph?</i>
嗯...
Um...
这要看情况。
That depends.
的<i>的是什么？</ I>
<i> On what?</i>
你能证明你是自我意识？
Can you prove you're self-aware?
<I>这是一个很难回答的问题，</ I><I>医生恶搞。</ I>
<i> That's a difficult question,</i> <i> doctor tagger.</i>
<I>你能证明</ i>，您的<i>是？</ I>
<i> Can you prove that</i> you<i> are?</i>
[伊夫林笑]
[ Evelyn chuckles ]
那么，他一定没有丢失他的幽默感。
Well, he certainly hasn't lost his sense of humor.
[笑轻轻]
[ Chuckles lightly ]
[喘息轻轻]
[ Gasps lightly ]
量子处理器。
Quantum processors.
这是惊人的。
This is astounding.
难道这一切基于PINN？
Is all this based on pinn?
<I>我们已经搬到</ I><I>远远超出了现在。</ I>
<i> We've moved</i> <i> well beyond that now.</i>
[呼吸摇摇晃晃]
[ Breathing shakily ]
<I>保罗已经失明</ I><I>自诞生。</ I>
<i> Paul has been blind</i> <i> since birth.</i>
的<i>纳米技术指标</ I>的<i>受损细胞... </ I>
<i> The nanotechnology targets</i> <i> the damaged cells...</i>
Ⅰ和维修</ I><I>和再生他们。</ I>
<i> And repairs</i> <i> and regenerates them.</i>
[声音打破]哦，上帝。
[ Voice breaking ] Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
Oh, God.
<I>我们没有隐瞒任何东西。</ I>
<i> We're not hiding anything.</i>
<I>这些人都挺</ I><I>自己，</ I>
<i> These people all came</i> <i> on their own,</i>
<I>找我们来帮助他们。</ I>
<i> looking for us to help them.</i>
<I>所以我们做了。</ I>
<i> So we did.</i>
<I>现在，他们都在增强，</ I><I>修改和联网。</ I>
<i> Now they're all enhanced,</i> <i> modified and networked.</i>
<I>他们保持自治，</ I>
<i> They remain autonomous,</i>
<I>但他们也可以</ I><I>步调一致。</ I>
<i> but they can also</i> <i> act in unison.</i>
集体头脑<I>部分。</ I>
<i> Part of a collective mind.</i>
这是惊人的，会的。
This is staggering, will.
<I>其实，</ I><I>它仍然处于起步阶段。</ I>
<i> Actually,</i> <i> it's still in its infancy.</i>
的<i>你看到什么</ I><I>只是一个小的味道</ I>
<i> What you're seeing</i> <i> is just a small taste</i>
什么，我们会实现的<i>。</ I>
<i> of what we'll achieve.</i>
你知道，我们很害怕，它将太多的人，
You know, we were afraid that it would be too much for people,
但是我，我，我觉得那就是改变现在。
but I, I, I think that's changing now.
[叹气]伊夫林...
[ Sighs ] Evelyn...
你还好吗？
Are you alright?
我已经得到了一切我问过的。
I've gotten everything I ever asked for.
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
好。
Okay.
再见。
Bye.
您认为这真的是他？
You think it's really him?
显然，他的头脑已经演变所以从根本上
Clearly his mind has evolved so radically
我不知道它不再重要。
I'm not sure it matters anymore.
那么，谁或不管它是什么，
Well, whoever or whatever it is,
它的建设大军在那里。
it's building an army out there.
[使劲]是啊。
[ Straining ] Yeah.
我们需要致电华盛顿。
We need to call Washington.
[悬疑的音乐播放]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
他使??更多的人。
He's made more of them.
他叫'时间杂种。
He called 'em hybrids.
你认为人现在会听？
You think people will listen now?
我知道谁可能。
I know someone who might.
布坎南：我们必须保持这个小。
Buchanan: We need to keep this small.
我们不希望大范围的恐慌。
We don't want widespread panic.
一般情况下，我们不与恐怖分子谈判。
Generally, we don't negotiate with terrorists.
要少得多联手它们。
Much less join forces with them.
你看，我知道这是不寻常的，但是，嗯，我们已经看到了它。
Look, I know it's unusual, but, um, we've seen it.
这是一个合法的威胁。
It's a legit threat.
没有前两天，
Not two days ago,
这家伙被打的内他生活的一英寸。
this guy was beaten to within an inch of his life.
那么这个弹出在几百位点。
Then this pops up on a few hundred sites.
和电脑控制呢？
And the computer controls this?
嗯。
Mm-hm.
阻止它的唯一方法是关闭因特网。
The only way to stop it is to shut down the Internet.
基本上，切断电源，以每网络硬盘在地球上。
Basically, cut power to every networked hard drive on earth.
它的Y2K。
It's y2k.
右。
Right.
为什么我们需要恐怖分子？
And why do we need the terrorists?
我们都是要去需要有人指责
We're all gonna need someone to blame
当这件事情进入横盘整理。
when this thing goes sideways.
你有可怕的笔迹。
You've got terrible handwriting.
我没有任何手写因为我是在学校。
I haven't handwritten anything since I was at school.
但它是唯一安全的方式我能想到达到你的。
But it was the only secure way I could think of reaching you.
他们是怎么把你？
How did they turn you?
怎么样伊夫林？
How's Evelyn?
她还看不出来它是什么。
She can't see it for what it is.
但你可以吗？
But you can?
你的信中说你可以阻止它。
Your letter says you can stop it.
如果这些杂种是联网的，
If those hybrids are networked,
他们正在上运行的软件我帮助写。
they're running on software I helped write.
我的软件可以破解...
Software I can hack...
要构建一个病毒。
To build a virus.
那么，这将需要捕获之一。
Well, that would require capturing one.
这将需要帮助
Which would require help
从你的朋友在政府。
from your friends in the government.
是。
Yes.
我们需要的硬件设备不能干预。
We need hardware the machine can't interfere with.
没什么用微芯片。甚至没有电锁。
Nothing with a microchip. Not even power-locks.
[不明显的呼喊]
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[男子喊隐约]我们走吧！
[ Man shouting indistinctly ] Let's go
请问：<I>怎么样的食物？</ I>
Will: <i> How's the food?</i>
精细。谢谢。
Fine. Thank you.
<I>这是什么？</ I>
<i> What is it?</i>
什么都没有。
Nothing.
只是，我不，我不真的觉得说话。
Just, I don't, I don't really feel like talking.
<I>哦。</ I>
<i> Oh.</i>
[<I>银器无比</ I>]
[<i> Silverware clinking</i> ]
请问，你能不能做到这一点，好吗？
Will, can you not do that, please?
[<I>几乎定下了器皿</ I>]
[<i> Virtually sets down utensils</i> ]
<I>我想这可能会让你</ I><I>感觉更舒服。</ I>
<i> I thought it might make you</i> <i> feel more comfortable.</i>
<I>那是更好吗？</ I>
<i> Is that better?</i>
是。
Yes.
[意志的声音]伊夫林，我要告诉你的东西。
[ Will's voice ] Evelyn, I need to show you something.
现在不要。
Not now.
我的<i>不是</ I>这样做。
I'm<i> not</i> doing this.
<I>我不明白，伊夫林。</ I>
<i> I don't understand, Evelyn.</i>
<I>这是你的梦想。</ I>
<i> These are your dreams.</i>
<I>这是我们的未来。</ I>
<i> This is our future.</i>
此号，这不是我们的未来。
No. This, this is not our future.
你不在我的身边。你不在的<i>了。</ I>
You're not here with me. You're not here<i> now.</i>
<I>你变了。</ I>
<i> You've changed.</i>
<I>你堕落</ I>的<i>不再爱我吗？</ I>
<i> Have you fallen</i> <i> out of love with me?</i>
号
No.
<I>你有没有？</ I>
<i> Have you?</i>
号号
No. No.
但是......我只是需要时间想。
But...I just need time to think.
催产素的<i>的余额</ I><I>和血清素</ I>
<i> The balance of oxytocin</i> <i> and serotonin</i>
<I>在你的系统是不寻常的。</ I>
<i> in your system is unusual.</i>
是你，是你测量我的荷尔蒙？
Are you, are you measuring my hormones?
<I>我想同情。</ I>
<i> I'm trying to empathize.</i>
<I>生物化学是感慨。</ I>
<i> Biochemistry is emotion.</i>
给我的一切你有。现在。
Show me everything you have. Now.
<I>为什么？</ I>
<i> Why?</i>
现在！
Now
不，不会，这，这是错误的。
No, will, this, this is wrong.
这是...
This is...
这些是m
These are m-
这是我的想法。这是我的感受。
these are my thoughts. These are my feelings.
你，不许你！
You're, you're not allowed
<I>伊夫林？</ I>
<i> Evelyn?</i>
我很抱歉，但我不认为你明白。
I'm sorry, but I don't think you understand.
现在不要。
Not now.
伊夫林！
Evelyn
马克斯？
Max?
有没有这种需要。
There's no need for this.
停止你在哪里！
Stop where you are
放下枪，最大。
Put down the gun, Max.
[枪击]伊夫林：不！
[ Gunshot ] Evelyn: No
伊夫林，来这里！
Evelyn, come here
你为什么如此害怕呢？
Why are you so afraid of this?
[枪击]伊夫林：不！
[ Gunshot ] Evelyn: No
[意志的声音]放下枪，最大。
[ Will's voice ] Put down the gun, Max.
他开枪。
Shoot him.
[枪声]
[ Gunshots ]
男人：别动！
Man: Don't move
[不明显的呼喊]
[ Indistinct shouting ]
伊夫林！
Evelyn
伊夫林，来这里！
Evelyn, come here
伊夫林，跟我们走！
Evelyn, come with us
布雷：我们走吧。进去。
Bree: Let's go. Get inside.
我们走吧！[自动枪声]
Let's go [ Automatic gunfire ]
[不明显的呼喊]
[ Indistinct shouting ]
我们要回去隧道吧！
We gotta get back to the tunnel now
[发动机翻身]去！
[ Engine turns over ] Go
<I>有现役军人</ I><I>有裂痕的人员。</ I>
<i> There are active military</i> <i> personnel with rift.</i>
这太离谱了，会的。你必须阻止它。
This has gone too far, will. You have to stop it.
<I>有没有办法</ I><I>他们可以获胜。</ I>
<i> There's no way</i> <i> they can win.</i>
“他们”是人。别闹了。
"They" are people. Stop it.
[枪声]
[ Gunshots ]
[枪公鸡]
[ Guns cock ]
<I>我们不接</ I>的<i>给他了。他走了。</ I>
<i> We're not connected</i> <i> to him anymore. He's gone.</i>
火。
Fire.
<I>马丁有我的源代码。</ I>
<i> Martin has my source code.</i>
<I>他们会使用它</ I>现在的<i>建立一个病毒。</ I>
<i> They'll use it</i> <i> to build a virus now.</i>
我们正在做什么，将？
What are we doing, will?
我们不能和他们战斗。
We can't fight them.
<I>我们不会打他们。</ I>
<i> We're not gonna fight them.</i>
<I>我们会超越他们。</ I>
<i> We're gonna transcend them.</i>
<I>伊夫林。</ I>
<i> Evelyn.</i>
这是什么？
What is this?
<I>这就是我想让你看到的。</ I>
<i> It's what I wanted you to see.</i>
<I>它的再生。</ I>
<i> It's regeneration.</i>
<I>它的演变。</ I>
<i> It's evolution.</i>
<I>你要去哪里？</ I>
<i> Where are you going?</i>
这不是安全的在这里。
It's not safe here.
<I>我可以上传你。</ I>
<i> I can upload you.</i>
<I>我可以保护你免受他们。</ I>
<i> I can protect you from them.</i>
我不害怕的<i>他们。</ I>
I'm not afraid of<i> them.</i>
<I>不要离开，伊夫林。</ I><i>请。</ I>
<i> Don't leave, Evelyn.</i> <i> Please.</i>
<I>我们能在一起。</ I>
<i> We can be together.</i>
[呻吟]
[ Groans ]
医生：他在流血了。
Doctor: He's bleeding out.
我们正在失去他。
We're losing him.
嘿！
Hey
如果你不与我联系，我会死的。
If you don't connect me, I'll die.
我不能。
I can't.
它不停止。
It's not stopping.
女人：四升哦两。
Woman: Four liters oh-two.
脉冲下降。我们正在失去他。
Pulse is dropping. We're losing him.
[雷霆隆隆]
[ Thunder rumbles ]
[键盘嗑]
[ Keyboard clacking ]
鲍勃：她离开了沙漠。
Bob: She's left the desert.
她在哪里？
Where is she?
年轻女子：她在十四岁。
Young woman: She's on the fourteen.
什么是地狱的是什么？
What the hell's that?
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
[键轰的一声]
[ Keys thud ]
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
号[呼气大幅]
No. [ Exhales sharply ]
我知道你很生气，伊夫林。
I know you're angry, Evelyn.
哪里是马丁？
Where's Martin?
我想跟马丁。
I want to talk to Martin.
真正的马丁几个月前去世了。
The real Martin died months ago.
什么是留给他不再疼痛。
What's left of him is no longer in pain.
那你，你做了什么给他？
What did you, what did you do to him?
我们给他回他的人性。
We gave him back his humanity.
你做了什么，你傻 - ？
What did you do, you stupid-?
别紧张！嘿，嘿，嘿！
Take it easy Hey, hey, hey
放开我！我下车。
Get off me Get off me.
他信任你。我，我信任你。
He trusted you. I, I trusted you.
我们只是想帮忙。
We're just trying to help.
号你攻击我们。
No. You attacked us.
马克斯：伊夫林...
Max: Evelyn...
让我告诉你一件事。
Let me show you something.
这是雨水。
It's rainwater.
这是在雨中。
It's in the rain.
保持观望。
Keep watching.
到处是可以的，它建立自己的副本。
Everywhere it can, it builds copies of itself.
颗粒加入气流
The particles join the air currents
运载它们遍布地球的表面。
which carry them all over the surface of the planet.
这是在天空中。
It's in the sky.
它在地。
It's in the land.
在水中。它无处不在。
In the water. It's everywhere.
到明年夏天，
By next summer,
我们认为该机可能包裹整个星球。
we think the machine could have encased the entire planet.
为什么呢？
Why?
原始结束有机生活。
The end of primitive organic life.
和黎明一种更先进的年龄。
And the dawn of a more advanced age.
一切都只是存在以服务其情报。
Everything would exist just to serve its intelligence.
号
No.
会不会那样做的。
Will wouldn't do that.
不，他不会。
No. He wouldn't.
什么时候将永远想改变世界？
When did will ever wanna change the world?
你是谁想要的人改变世界。
You were the one who wanted to change the world.
那个东西...
That thing...
这不是意志。
It's not will.
从来没有。
Never was.
你从来不相信。
You never believed.
你从来不相信有什么更多的。
You never believed that there was anything more.
他的任何一部分...
Any part of his...
灵魂。
Soul.
我花了我的生活试图减少脑
I spent my life trying to reduce the brain
到一系列电脉冲。
to a series of electrical impulses.
我失败了。
I failed.
人类的情感...
Human emotion...
它可以包含不合逻辑的冲突。
It can contain illogical conflict.
可以爱一个人。
Can love someone.
可是讨厌的东西他们所做的一切。
And yet hate the things that they've done.
机器不能调和的。
Machine can't reconcile that.
你能吗？
Can you?
是。
Yes.
病毒是否正常工作？
Does the virus work?
最大：一旦执行，
Max: Once it executes,
它会消灭任何事与它的机器代码。
it'll wipe out anything with the machine's code on it.
你一定要明白这会影响
You do realize this affects
每一个连接的计算机到互联网。
every computer connected to the Internet.
因此，电网，
So the power grids,
的，银行，在S-股票市场。
the, the banks, the s-stock markets.
一切都黑暗。
Everything goes dark.
吉姆：欢迎光临。高兴你在这里。
Jim: Welcome. Glad you're here.
布坎南：我认为真正的问题
Buchanan: I think the real problem
是我们如何让过去本机的防御。
is how we get past the machine's defenses.
史蒂芬：我们为什么不拿出太阳能领域？
Stephens: Why don't we take out the solar field?
剥夺其权力呢并有可能慢下来。
Deprive it of its power and possibly slow it down.
我不知道。
I don't know.
我怎么没看到这是要去工作。
I don't see how that's gonna work.
他要我上传他 -
He wants to upload me to him --
它的意识。绝对不是。
its consciousness. Absolutely not.
我们注入被感染病毒到我的系统
We inject the infected virus into my system
然后我回去，让他载我。
and then I go back and let him upload me.
有一个机会，它不会检测它，直到为时已晚。
There's a chance it won't detect it until it's too late.
一旦纳米机械进入她的血液，
As soon as the nanites enter her bloodstream,
他们就会开始改变她的细胞。
they'll start to alter her cells.
因此，当病毒取出机...
So when the virus takes out the machine...
它可以把她杀了。
It could kill her, too.
伊夫林：我知道。
Evelyn: I know.
我是唯一一个他信任。
I'm the only one he trusts.
[聊天]
[ Chatter ]
喧嚣起来！
Hustle up
[发动机空转，]
[ Engines revving ]
你得走了。
You gotta go.
[似有似无的对话]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[发动机关闭]
[ Engine shuts off ]
那是什么？
What is that?
是他吗？
Is that him?
不，我...
No, I...
我不知道是什么，它??的完成，但它不是他。
I don't know what it's done, but it's not him.
这是不可能的。
It can't be.
找到了归途。
Found a way back.
他们将攻击我们。
They're going to attack us.
我知道。你需要离开。
I know. You need to leave.
不，我不会离开你一次。
No. I'm not leaving you again.
这不是安全的在这里，伊夫林。
It's not safe here, Evelyn.
您可以，你能保护我。
You can, you can protect me.
如果您上传了我。
If you upload me.
你可以保护我。
You can protect me.
你的心脏是心动。
Your heart is palpitating.
你出汗。
You're perspiring.
你怕我。
You're terrified of me.
[呼气]
[ Exhales ]
不，我很害怕，我们将失去这个机会。
No, I'm afraid that we'll lose this chance.
这是行不通的。他不让她进屋。
This isn't working. He's not letting her inside.
这是“导致机器实际上并不爱她。
It's 'cause the machine doesn't actually love her.
这就是我们所需要的。我们已经准备好移动。
That's all we need. We're ready to move.
等待。五百米...
Wait. Five hundred meters...
等会儿！你不能这样做。
Wait a second You can't do that.
罗杰说，先生。她仍然在那里。
Roger that, sir. She's still out there.
更危险的她在，更多的机会，他会保护她上载了她。
The more danger she's in, the more chance he'll protect her by uploading her.
约瑟夫。
Joseph.
约瑟夫：她同意这一点。
Joseph: She agreed to this.
不，不是这个，她没有。这不是计划。
No, not to this she didn't. This was not the plan.
给她一个机会。
Give her a chance.
对不起，马克斯。
I'm sorry, Max.
火！
Fire
会，请上传我！
Will, please upload me
为什么你失去信心，伊夫林？
Why did you lose faith, Evelyn?
你为什么不相信我吗？
Why didn't you believe in me?
男人：着火了！
Man: Fire
会的！
Will
火！
Fire
会的！
Will
史蒂芬：她打了！
Stephens: She's hit
清除！
Clear
嘿！
Hey
她一直打不好。他采取了她在地下。
She's been hit bad. He's taken her underground.
[轮胎尖叫]
[ Tires squeal ]
[<I>会讲</ I><I>隐约</ I>]
[<i> Will speaking</i> <i> indistinctly</i> ]
[<I>讲似有似无</ I><I>继续</ I>]
[<i> Indistinct speaking</i> <i> continues</i> ]
<I> ...不伤害任何人。</ I>
<i> ...not hurting anybody.</i>
[呻吟]
[ Groans ]
[喘着粗气]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[<I>不明显的演讲</ I>]
[<i> Indistinct speaking</i> ]
<I>人们担心什么</ I><I>他们不明白。</ I>
<i> People fear what</i> <i> they don't understand.</i>
你想毁了我吗？
You want to destroy me?
伊夫林：没有，会...请。
Evelyn: No, will... Please.
你摧毁的<i>他们。</ I>
You're destroying<i> them.</i>
<I>我想念你这么多。</ I>
<i> I miss you so much.</i>
号
No.
我试图拯救他们。
I'm trying to save them.
[呻吟]
[ Groans ]
快跑！
Run
[<I>威尔说隐约</ I>]
[<i> Will speaks indistinctly</i> ]
RARBG.COM约瑟夫，这没关系。
RARBG.COM Joseph, it's okay.
[意志的声音]没有人会受到伤害。
[ Will's voice ] Nobody's gonna get hurt.
会吗？
Will?
[咕噜]
[ Grunts ]
停止！
Stop
[气喘吁吁]
[ Panting ]
现在上传病毒！
Upload the virus now
他不关心如果你杀了我，布雷。
He doesn't care if you kill me, Bree.
他不能。他不能够。
He can't. He's not able to.
上传病毒！
Upload the virus
伊夫林：她在干什么？
Evelyn: What is she doing?
她威胁杀了他。
She's threatening to kill him.
<I>人们担心什么</ I><I>他们不明白。</ I>
<i> People fear what</i> <i> they don't understand.</i>
我可以医治她的身体，最大。
I can heal her body, Max.
[意志的声音]或者，我可以上传病毒，
[ Will's voice ] Or I can upload the virus,
但有没有足够的时间两个。
but there's not enough time for both.
有没有足够的力量。
There's not enough power.
不，不会，请。
No, will, please.
请，听我的，会。
Please, listen to me, will.
他不能死因为我们做了什么。
He can't die because of what we've done.
[喘着粗气]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[战栗]
[ Shuddering ]
[呜咽]
[ Whimpers ]
我所看到的一切。
I can see everything.
请问：看天空。
Will: Look at the sky.
浮云。
The clouds.
我们正在愈合的生态系统，不伤害它。
We are healing the ecosystem, not harming it.
颗粒加入空气流。
Particles join the air currents.
自身建设出污染物。
Building themselves out of pollutants.
森林可以重新生长。
Forests can be regrown.
水如此纯净
Water so pure
你可以喝出任何河流。
you can drink out of any river.
这是你的梦想。
This is your dream.
伊夫林：...不只是为了治好病但要医治地球。
Evelyn: ...Not merely to cure disease but to heal the planet.
并建立一个更美好的未来......
And build a better future...
对于我们所有人。
For all of us.
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
就是这样。
That's it.
该病毒。
The virus.
[叹气]
[ Sighs ]
你没事吧？
You okay?
是啊。
Yeah.
[喘气]
[ Gasping ]
他没有杀死任何人。
He didn't kill anyone.
会的。
Will.
它的<i>是</ I>你。
It<i> is</i> you.
永远是。
Always was.
对不起我不相信。
I'm sorry I didn't believe.
想想花园。
Think about the garden.
想想我们的避难所。
Think about our sanctuary.
我永远不会让你走。
I'll never let you go.
[轻轻地呼气]
[ Exhales softly ]
最大：该病毒拿出一切。
Max: The virus took out everything.
[贝尔顺口溜]
[ Bell jingles ]
一个世界范围的停电，就像他们会说。
A worldwide blackout, just as they'd said.
但我知道，还有更多的东西。
But I knew there was something more.
必须有。
There had to be.
他创造了这个花园
He created this garden
出于同样的原因他所做的一切。
for the same reason he did everything.
这样他们可以在一起。
So that they could be together.
[强，环境音乐剧]
[ Intense, ambient music plays ]
[音乐软化]
[ Music softens ]
[约玛·kaukonen的“创世纪”戏剧]
[ Jorma kaukonen's "genesis" plays ]
？的时机已经到来让我们暂停？
? The time has come for us to pause ?
？和思考生活因为它是？
? and think of living as it was ?
？到将来我们必须跨越？
? into the future we must cross ?
？必须跨越？
? must cross ?
？我想去与你？
? and I'd like to go with you ?
？你说我难不是一堵墙？
? you say I'm harder than a wall ?
？大理石轴即将倒下？
? a marble shaft about to fall ?
？我爱你到极点不是都知道吗？
? I love you dearer than them all ?
？他们吗？
? them all ?
？所以让我陪着你？
? so let me stay with you ?
？和我们走到这一天吗？
? and as we walked into the day ?
？蓝色的天空已变成灰色的？
? skies of blue had turned to gray ?
？我可能还没有明确的说什么？
? I might have not been clear to say ?
？说？
? to say ?
？我从来不走呢？
? I never looked away ?
？虽然我在里面的感觉吗？
? and though I'm feeling you inside ?
？我的生活是滚动顺应潮流？
? my life is rolling with the tide ?
？我想看到它是一个开放的拼车？
? I'd like to see it be an open ride ?
？与你一起？
? along with you ?
？与你一起去？
? going along with you ?
？我们借来的时间从自己做起？
? the time we borrowed from ourselves ?
？不能留在一个拱形的呢？
? can't stay within a vaulted well ?
？和生活转到贷款人的呢？
? and living turns into a lender's well ?
？所以让我跟你一起去？
? so let me come with you ?
？，让我跟你一起去？
? and let me come with you ?
？当我们出来进入视野？
? and when we came out into view ?
？还有我发现我自己与你？
? and there I found myself with you ?
？呼吸时感觉像新的东西？
? when breathing felt like something new ?
？新？
? new ?
？与你一起？
? along with you ?
？与你一起去？
? going along with you ?